Finding Aid for the Theodore Payne Papers LSC.2368
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Nursery catalogs, 1895-1969; Series 9.
  - Rockmont Nursery: New or Noteworthy Plants, 1929 Autumn; Andrews, D.M. (Box 102)
  - Rockmont Nursery: New or Noteworthy Plants, 1934 Autumn to 1935 Spring; Andrews, D.M. (Box 102)
  - Suggestions for Effective Planting, 1917 January; Andorra Nurseries (Box 102)
  - Ground Cover Plants: Trees, Shrubs, and Evergreens; Rock Garden Plants and Herbaceous Perennials, 1931; Barclay, Hugh B. (Box 102)
  - Catalogo Descriptivo de Semillas Ponentinas para la Exportacion, undated; Barteldes Seed Co. (Box 102)
  - Spring Garden Book 1916, Berger, H.H. & Co. (Box 102)
  - 1917, Blake, Sherman T. Co. (Box 102)
  - Roses, 1925; Bobbink & Atkins (Box 102)
  - Hardy Herbaceous and Alpine Plants Retail Catalog, undated; Borsch & Son (Box 102)
  - Breck's High Grade Seeds: Everything for Farm, Garden and Lawn, 1918; Breck & Sons (Box 102)
  - Standard Grain, Seed, and Bean Cleaner, undated; Burch Plow Works Co. (Box 102)
  - Seeds for 1919, Burrell, D.V. (Box 102)
  - Wholesale Prices to Dealers, 1942 February 10; Burrell, D.V. (Box 102)
  - Burrell's Better Seeds 1957, Burrell, D.V. (Box 102)
  - Growers Price List: Primroses and Pansies, undated; Clarkes (Box 102)
  - Star Guide to Good Roses, 1926; Conard-Pyle Co. (Box 102)
  - Continuous Bloom in the Rock Garden: Acclimatized Plants, 1934; Cronamere Alpine Nurseries (Box 102)
  - Continuous Bloom in the Rock Garden: Acclimatized Plants, 1936; Cronamere Alpine Nurseries (Box 102)
  - Cronamere Alpine Nurseries, 1917; Dingee & Conard Co. (Box 102)
  - Wholesale Price List: Select Nursery Stock, 1938 Fall to 1939 Spring; Doty & Doerner, Inc. (Box 102)
  - Dreer's Garden Book 1916, Dreer, Henry A. (Box 102)
  - Dreer's Garden Book 1929, Dreer, Henry A. (Box 103)
  - Catalog of Plants, 1950; Fairchild Tropical Garden, The (Box 103)
  - Direction Book and Parts Price List for The "Clipper" Farm Grain and Seed Cleaners, undated; Ferrell, A.T. & Co. (Box 103)
    No. 1-B and No. 2-B
  - Clipper Cleaners for Grain, Seeds, and Beans, undated; Ferrell, A.T. & Co. (Box 103)
    Catalog 41
  - Every Garden Requisite, 1918; Alexander Forbes & Co. Seedsmen (Box 103)
  - 1932 Wholesale Prices, George Lawler Bulb Grower (Box 103)
  - Hardy Fern and Flower Farm, 1921 (Box 103)
  - Hardy Fern and Flower Farm, 1928; Gillett's (Box 103)
  - Tomato Tree, undated; Glecklers: Seedmen (Box 103)
  - Carnations and Mums, 1941; Henderson, Alec (Box 103)
  - Everything for the Garden, 1922; Henderson, Peter (Box 103)
  - Oak Sturdy Stock: Native Wild Flowers and Medicinal Plants, 1955; Henderson's Botanical Gardens (Box 103)
  - Seeds for Nurserymen: It's Perennial Time, 1957 Summer; Herbst Brothers (Box 103)
  - Seeds for Nurserymen: It's Perennial Time, 1959 Fall; Herbst Brothers (Box 103)
  - Wholesale Catalog of The D. Hill Nursery Co. Evergreen Specialists, 1917 Spring; Hill, D. Nursery Co. (Box 103)
  - Price-List of Cartareae, 1919; Kunze, Dr. Richard E. (Box 103)
  - Little England Daffodil Farm, undated (Box 103)
  - Novelty & General Catalog, 1916; Manda, W.A. Inc. (Box 103)
  - Contract List, 1938 April 12; McDowell, J.A. (Box 103)
  - Michell's Seeds, 1925; Michell, Henry F. Co. (Box 103)
  - Jobbers Special, undated; Mitchelhill Seed Co. (Box 103)
  - Catalog: Practical Books for Farmers, Flower and Vegetable Gardeners, Florists, Nurserymen, Stock Raisers, Dairymen, Fruit Growers, Poultrymen, Dog Fanciers, Housekeepers, Mechanics, Architects, Sportsmen, etc. and all People in Every Department of Human Endeavor, 1937 October 26; Orange Judd Publishing Co. (Box 103)
  - Alpine Gardens and Nursery, undated; Pacific Landscape Gardeners (Box 103)
  - Autumn Rarities in Seeds, Bulbs, and Plants, 1940; Pearce, Rex D. (Box 103)
    Offer 34B (1940)
  - Seeds, Plants, Bulbs: A Year Around Catalog, 1953; Pearce Seed Company (Box 103)
    Offer 59A (1953)
  - 1958 Wholesale Catalog of Fine Flower Seeds and Perennial Plants, Pearce Seed Company (Box 103)
  - Fourth Annual Flower Catalog 1914, Pomeray, Eltmeed (Box 103)
  - Quality Gardens: Iris, 1931 May 4; Quality Gardens (Box 103)
  - Catalogue 1894, Reid's Nurseries (Box 103)
  - Hardy Vines, Climbers, Creepers, Ferns, Aquatic and Bog Plants, Orchids, Bulbs, and Perennials, 1930 Autumn; Robbins, E.C. (Box 103)
  - Hardy Trees, Shrubs, Plants and Bulbs, 1951 Fall; Robbins, E.C. (Box 103)
  - Royal Poinciana Nurseries, Inc., 1916 (Box 103)
  - Catalog of Seeds, 1958 July; Saier, Harry E. (Box 104)
    No. 17 Issued July 1958
  - The Saier Catalog of Seeds, 1960 January; Saier, Harry E. (Box 104)
    No. 20 January 1960
  - John Scheepers Inc., 1927 Spring (Box 104)
  - Seeds for the Nurseryman and Forester, 1931 February 12; Schumacher, F.W. (Box 104)
  - Seeds for the Nurseryman and Forester, 1960-1961; Schumacher, F.W. (Box 104)
  - Seeds for the Nurseryman and Forester, 1961-1962; Schumacher, F.W. (Box 104)
  - Sherwood Nursery Co., 1961 Fall-1962 Spring (Box 104)
  - Seed Annual 1931, Stumpp & Walter Co. (Box 104)
  - 1916 Thorburn's Seeds, Thorburn's Seeds (Box 104)
  - Trade List 1920, Thorburn & Co.'s (Box 104)
  - The 120th Year of Thorburn's Seeds, 1921; Thorburn & Co.'s (Box 104)
  - Tingle's Wholesale Price List, 1939 Spring; Tingle Nursery Co. (Box 104)
  - Tingle's Wholesale Price List, 1961 Fall-1962 Spring; Tingle Nursery Co. (Box 104)
  - New List Prices on Henry Troemner's Balances, Scales, Weights for Chemists, Assayers, Druggists, Jewelers, 1920 February 16; Troemner's, Henry (Box 104)
  - Vaughan's Seed Store, 1918 (Box 104)
  - Vaughan's Green List 1940, Vaughan's Seed Store (Box 104)
  - Vaughan's Book for Florists, 1958 Autumn; Vaughan's Seed Store (Box 104)
  - Vaughan's Green List 1960, Vaughan's Seed Store (Box 104)
  - Vaughan's Dealers List, 1961 Spring; Vaughan's Seed Store (Box 104)
  - Plants and Snaps, 1961 June; Vaughan's Seed Store (Box 104)
  - Vaughan's Wholesale List, 1961 Spring; Vaughan's Seed Store (Box 104)
  - Wake Robin Farm: Wild Flowers and Ferns, 1955; Wake Robin Farm (Box 104)
  - 1931 Issue, Van Waveren, M. & Sons, Inc. (Box 104)
  - 1932 Issue, Van Waveren, M. & Sons, Inc. (Box 104)
  - Hardy Plants Roses, Shrubs, Bulbs, 1958 Spring; Wayside Gardens Co. (Box 104)
  - Criadero de Arboles, 1941; El Vergel (Box 105)
  - Price List: Finest Quality Bulbs, undated; R.M. Palmer (Box 105)
  - Catalogue of South African Seeds and Bulbs, 1931 April 27; Stanford, K.C. (Box 105)
  - Fruit & Timber-Growing in the Nile Valley, undated; Traders and Growers' Union (Box 105)
  - Trade Catalogue of Seeds and Bulbs, 1919-1920; Wildpret Bros. (Box 105)